var triviaALL =[
    {
        question: "What is the name of Hermione's club to help house elves?",
        answer: "Society for the Promotion of Elfish Welfare",
        wrongs: ["House Elf Liberation Front", "Association of House Elf Aid and Defense", "Labor Union for the Treatment of Elves"]
    },
    {
        question: "How many dementors attacked Harry and Dudley in Little Whinging?",
        answer: 2,
        wrongs: [1,3,4]
    },
    {
        question: "What color did Ron try to turn Scabbers the day that he and Harry met on the Hogwarts Express?",
        answer: "yellow",
        wrongs: ["red","orange","blue"]
    },
    {
        question: "In book 1, what was the date of the Gringotts break-in?",
        answer: "31 July",
        wrongs: ["17 June","1 September","13 August"]
    },
    {
        question: "What's the name of Hagrid's dog",
        answer: "Fang",
        wrongs: ["Crookshanks","Pickett","Scabbers"]
    },
    {
        question: "How many silver Sickles in a Galleon",
        answer: "17",
        wrongs: ["19","10","15"]
    },
    {
        question: "What was James Potter's nickname when he was at Hogwarts?",
        answer: "Prongs",
        wrongs: ["Moony","Wormtail","Padfoot"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the password to the secret passageway to Honeydukes?",
        answer: "Dissendium",
        wrongs: ["Alohomora","Diffindo","Revlio"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which victim of Slytherin's monster was found on Halloween night?",
        answer: "Mrs. Norris",
        wrongs: ["Colin Creevy","Justin Finch-Fletchley","Penelope Clearwater"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the title of Gilderoy Lockhart's autobiography?",
        answer: "Magical Me",
        wrongs: ["Gadding with Ghouls","Prefects Who Gained Power","Gilderoy The Savior"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ron's Quidditch team?",
        answer: "Chudley Cannons",
        wrongs: ["Puddlemere United","Tutshill Tornados","Holyhead Harpies"]
    },
    {
        question: "What is Lily Potter's patronus?",
        answer: "Doe",
        wrongs: ["Stag","Dog","Rabbit"]
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the Divination classroom?",
        answer: "North Tower",
        wrongs: ["Astronomy Tower","Seventh Floor Corridor","Dungeons"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which dragon did Fleur Delacour battle?",
        answer: "Welsh Green",
        wrongs: ["Chinese Fireball","Hungarian Horntail","Swedish Short-Snout"]
    },
    {
        question: "What was the answer to the Sphinx's riddle in the thrid Tri-Wizard Task?",
        answer: "Spider",
        wrongs: ["Point Me","Boggart","Midnight"]
    },
    {
        question: "Where is the headquarters of the Order of the Phoenix",
        answer: "Number twelve, Grimmauld Place",
        wrongs: ["Number four, Privet Drive","Tottenham Court Road","8 Heathgate, Hampstead Garden"]
    },
    {
        question: "What was the row number in the Department of Mysteries where Harry's prophecy was stored?",
        answer: "97",
        wrongs: ["85", "131","76"]
    },
    {
        question: "Which educational decree created the office of Hogwarts High Inquisitor?",
        answer: "23",
        wrongs: ["22", "24","25"]
    },
];
